Eugenia Karpova

Frontend Developer

Remote/relocate (currently in Moscow, Russia)
ohneika@gmail.com | linkedIn | telegram/whatsapp: @ohnejka

Summary

Looking for challenging frontend architecture development tasks.

Stack: Vue/Nuxt and Angular2 (production experience), Typescript, React and Redux (pet projects), GraphQl, Three.js.

I've been doing frontend development since 2018 (changed my career back then), worked in 2 studios. Got Site of the day on Awwwards. Have been on Frontend TL position for the last 6 months.

Work Experience

Frontend Team Lead at PINKMAN (pinkman.ru)

Nov 2021 - Apr 2022

Stack: Vue/Nuxt, Typescript, GraphQl, React, Redux, Miro

- architecture engineering, data modeling, developing frontend components,
- project leading, workload planning, communication with project managers and design team
- team leading of 2-4 junior and middle frontend developers, code review, hard & soft skills development, projects retrospective

Frontend Developer at PINKMAN (pinkman.ru)

Nov 2020 - Nov 2021

Stack: Vue/Nuxt, Typescript, GraphQl, Figma

- cross browser and adaptive web components development (figma to web)
- preparing API in backend-for-frontend admin panel

Frontend Developer at Fluc28 (<u>facebook.com/fluc28</u>)

Apr 2019 - Sep 2020

Stack: Angular, Typescript, Three.js, .NET, C#, Cinema4D, WebGl, SparkAR

- cross browser and adaptive web components development
- taking part in architecture planning of websites with integrated 3d scenes, integration of 3d-world actions with user actions e.g camera moves with routing changes. Adapted webgl shaders a bit.
- created custom CMS frontend-side and prepared API

Supply Planner at Adidas Group CIS (www.adidas-group.com)

Sep 2017 - Oct 2018

- stock planning & supply forecasting of Football goods category
- SAP MM key user (system upgrade, regression tests)
- continuous logistics support during World Cup 2018 in Russia

Supply planner at Bosch Russia (www.bosch.ru)

Apr 2016 - Jul 2018

- rough distribution for Georgia and Kazakhstan
- monthly demand forecast & supply planning for 12 months (rolling year), ~2000 SKUs.
- S&OP activities, consensus forecasting

Languages

English - advanced | French - intermediate | Russian - native

Education

Higher education

National Research University - Higher School of Economics (www.hse.ru/en)
Faculty of World Economy and International Affairs, International Affairs (2007 - 2012)

Professional development courses

2021: Advanced Frontend. Architecture of large frontend application (4 months course)